Those of us who are involved in the global battle against imperialism
know that such setbacks are only temporary.
They are not permanent defeats,
because they cannot halt the tide of resistance.
The liberation struggle in Guinea-Bissau continues to rage on
and will ultimately defeat Portuguese colonialism,
like the coup d'etat in Ghana when Nkrumah was deposed,
like the terrible slaughter of the thousands of revolutionaries in Indonesia.
The assassination of Cabral can only be a temporary defeat.
And I think that any of you who would sit down
and seriously study the international scene
would see that today the trend of history is very clear.
What happened on that day, on December 4th in the United Nations,
what happened when the resolution in support of armed struggle against colonialism was passed,
was a mirror of the forces of history.
There is no doubt about the fact that history has already sided with the forces of revolution,
the forces of national liberation,
the forces of socialism.
And through the protests and battles of millions abroad,
and in this country as well,
history has indicted imperialism.
History has indicted U.S. imperialism
and has already condemned it to its grave.
The purpose of the world as well,
history has been at the infinity-might to the village of modernism sites,
and at the same time of the world,
history has been pretty much more very beneficial.
The purpose of the movement has been against the government現在,
and the government has been against the government,
the government has been buildingctures and political Afghans,
and the republicans has been created to the government.
This is not an truth,
the government has been Ewangelism and the people who have tried to do well with this.
It has been a lot of times about the government now.
The government has been against the government,
and it has been given it to the government.
But if you haven't discussed the government,